[{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8026,"timeElapsed":23586},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3966,"timeElapsed":27559},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3506,"timeElapsed":31074},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":8163,"timeElapsed":39243},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":8381,"timeElapsed":47633},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6848,"timeElapsed":54487},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5941,"timeElapsed":60436},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":11799,"timeElapsed":72243},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4808,"timeElapsed":77058},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7222,"timeElapsed":85618},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4406,"timeElapsed":90032},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4422,"timeElapsed":94463},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6141,"timeElapsed":100613},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8640,"timeElapsed":109262},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":11648,"timeElapsed":120919},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4287,"timeElapsed":125212},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6783,"timeElapsed":132001},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4310,"timeElapsed":136317},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":8447,"timeElapsed":146132},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4130,"timeElapsed":150267},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":153830},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4836,"timeElapsed":158672},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4824,"timeElapsed":163504},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5124,"timeElapsed":168637},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9606,"timeElapsed":178251},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":12018,"timeElapsed":190277},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4667,"timeElapsed":194951},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":6617,"timeElapsed":203649},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":206239},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4805,"timeElapsed":211049},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5597,"timeElapsed":216653},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":219704},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806607,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9600,"timeElapsed":229309},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7763,"timeElapsed":237077},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3557,"timeElapsed":240643},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5699,"timeElapsed":246350},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2959,"timeElapsed":249315},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7797,"timeElapsed":258747},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2918,"timeElapsed":261672},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2908,"timeElapsed":264587},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5148,"timeElapsed":269740},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":8057,"timeElapsed":277804},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5258,"timeElapsed":283067},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3522,"timeElapsed":286594},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5067,"timeElapsed":291666},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4801,"timeElapsed":296476},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9784,"timeElapsed":308466},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980890309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4540,"timeElapsed":313012},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":316262},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980898360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4797,"timeElapsed":321062},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5375,"timeElapsed":326445},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980911866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":8118,"timeElapsed":334568},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6919,"timeElapsed":341492},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980927386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8590,"timeElapsed":350089},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6213,"timeElapsed":356306},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980941722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4913,"timeElapsed":364425},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":9784,"timeElapsed":374216},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4649,"timeElapsed":378869},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980961949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5778,"timeElapsed":384652},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980966507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4554,"timeElapsed":389210},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":9520,"timeElapsed":398736},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980990088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":14047,"timeElapsed":412790},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10299,"timeElapsed":423095},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981010408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10011,"timeElapsed":433111},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4869,"timeElapsed":440503},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981023897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6092,"timeElapsed":446600},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4252,"timeElapsed":450858},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981032770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4607,"timeElapsed":455473},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5564,"timeElapsed":461042},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981048020,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9674,"timeElapsed":470723},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":12408,"timeElapsed":483136},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":9033,"timeElapsed":492178},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7167,"timeElapsed":499351},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":502899},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981089337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7093,"timeElapsed":512040},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981091913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":514616},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4549,"timeElapsed":519172},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981100877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4402,"timeElapsed":523580},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981106152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5267,"timeElapsed":528855},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981112044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5886,"timeElapsed":534747},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981118900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6848,"timeElapsed":541603},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981125215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6309,"timeElapsed":547918},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981132407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7186,"timeElapsed":555110},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981141373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6894,"timeElapsed":564076},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981144738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":567441},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981147262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":569965},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981153719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":6451,"timeElapsed":576422},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981162701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8970,"timeElapsed":585403},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981169142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6433,"timeElapsed":591845},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981176775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7627,"timeElapsed":599478},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981181939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5158,"timeElapsed":604642},{"subjectID":"vohoutxnom","prolificID":"66a7abb383fda32ced03e410","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24b13ce4861332cf28c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981188372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6428,"timeElapsed":611075}]